infoisinfo.co.in 2014-06-25

# Privacy policy Infoisinfo

In compliance with the provisions set forth in the Personal Data Protection Organic Law 15/1999 of the Spanish Legislation, users of the site [www.Infoisinfo.co.in](http://www.infoisinfo.co.in/), are made aware of our policy on the management of personal data in order to guarantee and protect the information collected. 

Infoisinfo.co.in Infoisinfo.co.in is property of COMERLEADS S.L., which is owner of and responsible for the database generated from public sources and with the personal information provided by users. 

By pressing SEND, you agree that the personal data you have provided to us is added on a file owned by COMERLEADS, S.L. The purpose of such file is to provide you with the services indicated in the page, send you commercial or advertising information relative to our services and send you commercial or advertising information relative to services and products you have requested, by any means of communication (by phone, SMS, electronic means, etc.). Likewise, with the purpose of making you aware of the offers relative to their services, you expressly authorise your data to be assigned to the company or companies from which you have requested information. 

If you do not wish to receive information or if you wish to correct or remove your data from our file, please let us know by sending an e-mail to users@infoisinfo.co.in or by mail to COMERLEADS, S.L. Calle Alejandro González, 5 – 6º B - 28028 Madrid [Address is in Spanish for mailing purposes], clearly indicating the reason for your letter, your name, surnames and address. 

COOKIES

In order to expedite the service provided, COMERLEADS, S.L. will use cookies to offer you a better and more personalised service. This cookie is installed when the navigation session on any of our Infoisinfo Sites starts. If the User does not wish that a cookie is saved on his hard disk, he must adjust his browser settings accordingly by using the procedure recommended by his browser or eliminate it directly from his computer. In this case, the speed and quality of the operation of the services of COMERLEADS, S.L. may decrease.COMERLEADS, S.L. will save your typical navigation route to adapt our services as much as possible to your preferences. The User expressly agrees to the use of cookies by COMERLEADS, S.L. with no need to request his consent each time he enters any of our Sites. The cookies sent to you are stored in your PC. The names of the servers that transmit or activate the data collection automatic procedures are under the domain Infoisinfo.co.in 

Data Requested and Treatment

Right to Information

When the company or the user decide to register in the database of Comerleads, S.L., they are requested to provide only the data strictly necessary to achieve the purpose for which our Web is intended, which is to solely facilitate the communication between companies and users to allow them to contract the services and products of companies. To that effect, users will be required to send their needs on this company, which involves providing some personal information such as: name, address, telephone, e-mail, and other, necessary to achieve the purpose for which our Web is intended, which is to solely facilitate the communication between companies and users to allow them to contract the services and products of companies. The treatment of such data will be focused only on the achievement of that purpose, always within the established regulatory framework. By sending the information, the user agrees to the treatment thereof under the conditions described in the section of Privacy Control. 

Privacy Control

The user will have control over his data and will be able to access the Site at any time to modify his data and even to request the cancellation of use thereof by Infoisinfo.co.in. 

User’s Consent

By pressing the “SEND” button on the data collection forms, the user shall be deemed to have accepted the established terms and conditions. The personal data collected from our users is stored in a database owned by Comerleads, S.L., which guarantees proper technical and structural measures to prevent the integrity and security of the personal information provided. The information collected is adequate, appropriate and non-excessive in relation to the specific, explicit and legal scope, purposes and services on the Web Infoisinfo.co.in. 

Right to Opposition, Correction and Updating of Data

The user has the right to access this information, to modify it if the data is incorrect, and to deregister from the file. In the latter case, Comerleads, S.L. automatically loses the information. These rights can be immediately enforced once the user states his express intention of deregistering. 

In the case of problems in the online effective performance, or for any kind of inquiry or controversy related to our data privacy policy, you may contact us directly: 

By e-mail: users@infoisinfo.co.in   
By phone: (+34) 910149822  
By mail:COMERLEADS, S.L.  
Calle Alejandro González, 5 – 6º B  
28028 Madrid (Spain)
